Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Chemistry, Records SC0687
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Chemistry, records
1964-2002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of Chemistry
SC0687
3 Linear Feet
These records consist of lists of graduate students, post-doctoral fellows, and visiting scholars, 1964-2002; and photographs (mostly photocopies) of graduate students, 1966-2002.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Administrative transfer, 2003.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
These records consist of lists of graduate students, post-doctoral fellows, and visiting scholars, 1964-2002; and photographs (mostly photocopies) of graduate students, 1966-2002.
Stanford University -- General subdivision--Students.;; Stanford University. Department of Chemistry; Stanford University. Department of Chemistry
- Records, 1964-2002
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lists of graduate students and post-doctoral associates, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photos of first-year graduate students, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Photos of first-year graduate students, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photos of first-year graduate students, 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photos of first-year graduate students, 1991-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photos of first-year graduate students, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Visting Scholars, 1965-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Visting Scholars, 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Visting Scholars, 1990-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Additional Records, 1980-2002; Accession ARCH-2017-101
  - Course Reader: Chemistry 33, Section I, Jim Collman, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Course Reader: Introduction to Organic Chemistry: A different perspective on key concepts, by Professor James P. Collman, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Course Reader: Chem 130: Getting Started in Chemistry 130/132, Jonathan Touster; Justin Dubois, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Course Reader: Chem 130/132, Professor Jonathan Touster & Dr. Elliad Silcoff, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Course Reader: Chem 130/132: Theory and Practice of Identification: Qualitative Organic Analysis, Professor Jonathan Touster; Thomas Wandless, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Course Reader: Chem 130/132: Theory and Practice of Identification: Qualitative Organic Analysis, Professor Jonathan Touster; Thomas Wandless, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Course Reader: Chem 32: Frontiers in Chemistry, Professor James Collman; Professor Richard Zare, 2002 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-288
  - Faculty Awards, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Department Statistics, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Summer Biotechnology Conference, 2002 Jul 25 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Night Live Chemwipes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Guide to the Zare Labs, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Student Handbook, circa 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, 1960s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Majoring in Chemistry, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Swan Building Plans, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Swan Building Plans, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Postdoc/Grad student list, 1999 Oct 11 (Box 2)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted for 75 years from date of creation.